When Allah created the heavens and the earth , he created Humans from clay and Angels from light
But he created another being from fire . Djinn
Allah has seperated Man from Djinn
But sometimes , their worlds come together , and this always causes great suffering
Khalid needs to be close to his family .
He knows how this will make you stronger .
It 's time . Listen to him .
You must return .
You can 't deny the past .
It 's what makes us who we are .
If you won 't accept it ..
.. how will we have a future ?
You must go back . It 's time .
You 're not thinking clearly . It is time .
Khalid must return .
You will not stand in my way .
How can you reject a request from the man you love ?
We won !
Tell your American friend not to make fun of this matter .
I only came here for you .
If this continues , I swear I 'm leaving .
Or more likely to change his diaper .
We thought you 'd never get here .
Welcome home Khalid .
Thank you , sir .
It was a long flight .
Well , you 're back in civilization now .
Welcome home sweetie .
Come. the car is right outside .
So did you hear ? Yasmin had a baby ?
No .
So did Afra .
And Maitha .
All your old friends .
What ?
I just want to be a grandmother .
Well ...
Now that you 're back ...
it wouldn 't hurt to go for an Umrah ...
so God will bless your new life here .
God willing .
Nasser , don 't drive so fast .
I 'm going five miles an hour .
Any slower and we 'll stop .
So how did you find the place ?
My company found it .
They got it all set up .
But why Al Hamra ?
They just tore down the old village .
How fast were they able to build a new tower here ?
Yes , can you believe it ?
They built it
right on the djinn village .
They have no respect .
Whatever .
It 's a new building ... on the beach .
A great place for a vacation .
Khalid
Are you going to make that long drive everyday ?
I don 't get it .
Why didn 't they put you in the city ?
They said it 's nice .
The Palm is nice .
Abu Dhabi is nice .
But this ?
Daddy ! What are you doing ?
Someone was standing in the middle of the road !
I could have killed him .
He looked ...
Don 't get out !
He might be hurt .
Stay here , sir . I 'll look .
How is anyone supposed to find this place , Khalid ?
Does anyone else live here
It 's new .
It 's probably like every other project built out here , all bought up by the Gulf Arabs .
And they 're not here but in winter .
Then you 'll wish if it was deserted .
I don 't trust that Sammy guy .
Why not ?
He 's too friendly . He wants something .
You watch out , Salama .
Nice !
They 've put a lot of effort into this place .
Come .
Welcome .
Oh my ...
What a beautiful place .
You 'll have a nice view of the sea
if the fog ever clears .
You know I 'm afraid of heights .
You know what this place need ?
It needs this .
You never know who might visit .
What ?
It wards off envy .
It can 't hurt , right ?
Thank you . Mamma .
It 's ... very nice of you .
And this ...
.. will help ward off evil .
Hang it over the entrance .
Yes , Momma .
Come on
let 's see the rest .
They sure pulled out all the stops .
Looks like a lot of effort .
They did a nice job .
There 's more down here !
For my grandchildren .
What happened ?
There was a bird .
But I thought it was something else .
Someone .
On the sixth floor ?
Probably one of those window washers .
I know their kind ...
They 're perverts .
Peeking in when I take a bath .
Don 't you wish .
Come on . It 's time to go .
Why don 't you stay a little longer ?
At least until the fog clears .
We have to go .
You two must rest .
I have some work at the office .
We 'll be back tomorrow .
Enjoy your new home .
Welcome back , Khalid .
I don 't know how you convinced her to return . Thank you so much .
It wasn 't easy sir .
That flight is brutal .
Now what ? What is wrong with you ?
We 're going to die !
Great ...
That 's the spirit .
Always optimistic .
Come on ! Start , you piece of ...
Daddy , I 'm calling Salama and Khalid .
Okay . Call them .
That 's weird .
I 'll call a tow truck .
We 're in the middle of the desert !
The phones won 't work !
Of course they 'll work .
We just left the building .
And anyway , this is satellite ...
What ? What ? What is it
Well ? What 's the problem ?
What is wrong with you ?
There ' someone out there .
There is no one outside .
Don 't be like your sister .
Nasser .
Daddy ! Please don 't !
What ? What 's the problem ?
Don 't go out there .
We are in the middle of the dessert .
What could possibly be there ?
No !
I will not have my family treated like this !
Daddy ! Don 't !
Let me go !
Where are you ?
Where are you , you cowards ?
You want Nasser ?
Come get me !
Come on ! You got Nasser to deal with now !
Where are you , you cowards ?
Where are you ?
This is bullshit !
Bullshit .
Not America .
At least , try .
Khalid , I 'm going crazy .
I can 't believe I 'm saying this , but ..
I 'm beginning to believe the stories .
In the name of God ,
the most gracious ,
the merciful ...
Praise be to God
the Cherisher ... and ... and ...
I ask for God 's forgiveness .
In the name of God , the most gracious ,
the merciful ,
I seek refuge in the Lord of ...
I seek refuge in the Lord of Mankind
the King of mankind ,
the true God of mankind ,
from the evil of the sneaking whisperer ,
who whispereth in the hearts of mankind ,
of the djinn and mankind .
God is the greatest .
Glorified is my lord , the almighty
God listens to those who are grateful .
God is the greatest .
Glory be to God exalted .
How did you get in here ?
Your door was open .
It has been a long time since I 've seen you pray Salama .
Where 's Daddy ?
Outside .
There is something important I needed to tell you . I couldn 't wait .
It 's about the child .
Many couples have suffered the loss of an infant child , Salama .
I know .
And of course you want kids .
Why haven 't you tried again ?
I 'm just not ready .
Not ready ...
.. to see another child that looks like your previous baby ?
Murder is a sin , Salama .
How did you know ?
I didn 't mean to hurt him .
Then what did you mean ?
Go clean yourself .
Hello ?
Hello . I need to speak to Salama Zakaria
Salama speaking ...
This is the police . I am sorry to report ... there has been a terrible accident .
I can 't talk about it now .
I need to be alone .
Then walk me to the car .
And come say bye to your family .
I love you .
Murder is a sin .
I didn 't say anything .
You just moved in here today , didn 't you ?
Yes .
How did you know ?
There aren 't many people living in this building .
I 've never met you before .
Are you from Ras Al Khaima ?
Yes , I am .
How did you know ?
We used to live here .
But my parents moved when the village was torn down .
But
they couldn 't get rid of me .
Well , I 'm glad .
I must have forgotten to press my floor ...
More time to chat .
What a coincidence .
I 'm on the sixth floor too .
I met your wife today .
She told me about you .
There 's not much to tell .
Oh come on ...
I 'll have to find out some other way .
You do that ...
If you have to .
I 'll help you .
And why not ?
Hi again !
Hello .
What a pleasant surprise .
Who 's there ?
Who are you ?
Well ..
Did you forget me , Khalid ?
Police . How can we help you ?
Look , I know this sounds crazy but ...
I can 't find my wife .
I think something bad has happened .
Where are you calling from , sir ?
The Al Hamra .
We just moved into the new building .
I am here .
I told you that call was nothing .
This place won 't be open for months .
Can 't you hear me ?
I am here .
Well , we had to check it . You heard the screams from the call .
And now that we checked it , can we please go ?
This place gives me the creeps .
I 'm here right in front of you !
Come back !
What 's your problem ?
Don 't tell me you never heard any stories about Al Hamra ...
Help me ! Help me please !
It 's time .
She 's inside me , Khalid .
Who ?
Who is she ?
She 's making me do this .
She 's coming .
Khalid , help me !
You were taken away from me once .
But I never gave up on you .
I kept looking for you .
Come back to me .
Didn 't she kill your son ?
She deserves to die .
True .
You know what to do .
You killed my son !
You are one of them .
Please God , save me .
Don 't say god 's name .
He was our son !
And you killed him !
Feed your anger .
Feed on your hatred .
Embrace your true nature .
You took him away from me .
As I was taken away from my mother .
But she kept looking for me .
Unlike you ..
A mother sacrifices for her child .
You 're not a mother !
You 're a monster .
Blood for blood .
A life for a life .
This is my home , I 'm back .